<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Objects encoded with the <gi>object</gi> Element</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Working draft - Published (preliminarily) on GitHub</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Written by Suzanne Raybuck as a part of her Editing, Writing, and Media internship (with Sarah Stanley)</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text>
      <body>
         <p>
            <listObject>
               <object>
                  <objectIdentifier>
                     <country>United States of America</country>
                     <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                     <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                     <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                     <objectName>Ceramic Penguin</objectName>
                  </objectIdentifier>
                  <physDesc>
                     <objectDesc>
                        <p>The <objectType>figurine</objectType> stands about <height unit="inch"
                              quantity="8">8 inches</height> in height and is composed of a penguin
                           standing on top of a misshapen rock. It is made out of
                              <material>ceramic</material> material and has a shiny, glazed surface.
                           The penguin stands with its flippers placed on its hips, and its head
                           cocked at a slight angle. Its feet are painted onto the rock it stands
                           upon, which is grey/green, about <height unit="inch" quantity="2">2
                              inches</height> tall, and textured with tiered grooves. This texturing
                           leads to the rock being very misshapen on the sides but smooth on top.
                           There are also small holes of about <dim unit="centimeter" quantity="1">1
                              centimeter</dim> in diameter in various spots on the rock. The rock
                           part of the figurine is hollow while the penguin is not. </p>
                     </objectDesc>
                     <decoDesc>
                        <p>The penguin is decorated with black paint on its face and tips of its
                           flippers, blue paint on its back and flippers, white on its stomach and a
                           fine line of yellow where its head meets its back.</p>
                     </decoDesc>
                  </physDesc>
               </object>
               <object>
                  <objectIdentifier>
                     <country>United States of America</country>
                     <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                     <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                     <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                     <objectName>Navy Plane Model</objectName>
                  </objectIdentifier>
                  <physDesc>
                     <objectDesc>
                        <p>A lightweight <objectType>model</objectType> of the Ford Trimotor
                           aircraft outfitted with skis. <damage>The model is missing its left
                              landing ski and its central front propeller.</damage> The model is
                           made out of some kind of <material>plastic</material> and its body and
                           wings are painted to resemble silver, corrugated metal with visible
                           riveting around the windows.</p>
                     </objectDesc>
                     <typeDesc>
                        <p>On the top and underside of the right wing there is the identification
                           number “NX4542” printed in large, bolded, red letters. On either side of
                           the body of the plane there is the text “ANTARCTIC EXPEDITION” in
                           capitalized, bolded letters. Beneath the Ford logo there is “TRI - MOTOR”
                           in small, black bolded text.</p>
                     </typeDesc>
                     <decoDesc>
                        <p>The nose of the plane is blue, the propellors have red tips and black
                           blades, the landing skis are brown, and the motors are black. On either
                           side of the vertical fin of the tail, there is the Ford company logo.</p>
                     </decoDesc>
                  </physDesc>
               </object>
               <object>
                  <objectIdentifier>
                     <country>United States of America</country>
                     <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                     <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                     <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                     <objectName>Navy Icebreaker Model</objectName>
                  </objectIdentifier>
                  <physDesc>
                     <p>A detailed <objectType>model</objectType> of a wind-class ice breaker ship.
                        The hull of the ship is painted red while there is grey paint on the sides
                        above the waterline and on the roof, the deck is a light tan color and the
                        small propellers at the back of the ship are gold. The ship is labelled
                        “GB3” in four places along the waterline of the ship, two at either side of
                        the bow and two at the stern.</p>
                     <!--deck-->
                     <ab>Around the entire deck are small guard rails.</ab>
                     <!--bow-->
                     <ab>At the bow there is a large, gray, armored gun that sits in the center of
                        the deck. Behind it are two smaller, black, unshielded guns.</ab>
                     <!--starboard and port-->
                     <ab>On the starboard and port sides there are lifeboats with cranes.</ab>
                     <!--stern-->
                     <ab>At the stern, there is a helipad and helicopter hangar with a small orange
                        model of a Sikorsky naval helicopter. At the stern railing there is a small
                        American flag flying. </ab>
                     <!--center-->
                     <ab>At the center of the ship there is a large radar unit, broken mast with a
                        variety of maritime flags flying and a large ventilation shaft.</ab>
                     <objectDesc>
                        <supportDesc>
                           <support>There is an orange, plastic support underneatht the model so it
                              can stand level. The support is T-shaped with poles extending from
                              three end points on the T to meet the hull of the ship.</support>
                        </supportDesc>
                     </objectDesc>
                  </physDesc>
               </object>
               <object>
                  <objectIdentifier>
                     <country>United States of America</country>
                     <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                     <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                     <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                     <objectName>Armored Vehicle</objectName>
                  </objectIdentifier>
                  <physDesc>
                     <objectDesc>
                        <p>A small <objectType>model</objectType> of a rectangular armored vehicle
                           with treads. Within the treads there are twelve wheels on each side. The
                           driver and passenger side doors are printed with the text “USN54-25026”.
                           The cabin of the vehicle is shaped like a rectangular prism with seven
                           glassless, rectangular windows; two on each side, one in the front and
                           one in the back. Inside the driver’s seat there is a small bar apparatus
                           for steering, there is no seat in the passenger side and instead it is
                           blocked with a console. The front hood has a tow hook and winch,
                           headlights and a few other various mechanical apparatuses. The back trunk
                           has a model fire axe and shovel attached to it. <damage>The top of the
                              vehicle has an antenna that has been bent flat. At several of the hard
                              corners and edges of the truck, the paint has been touched up with a
                              slightly different shade of orange.</damage>
                        </p>
                     </objectDesc>
                     <decoDesc>
                        <p>It is almost entirely painted orange except for its treads which are
                           black and the suspension wheels within the treads which are green.</p>
                     </decoDesc>
                  </physDesc>
               </object>
               <object>
                  <objectIdentifier>
                     <country>United States of America</country>
                     <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                     <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                     <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                     <objectName>Emergency Lantern</objectName>
                  </objectIdentifier>
                  <physDesc>
                     <objectDesc>
                        <p>A large, <material>metal</material> emergency
                              <objectType>lantern</objectType> that is about <dim unit="feet"
                              quantity="1">1 foot</dim> tall. It is silver colored metal with a
                           tarnished, dirty exterior. The lantern has a circular fuel tank base that
                           is about <dim unit="inch" quantity="2">2 inches</dim> tall with HERCULES
                           printed in large letters on the front of it. There is also a small fuel
                           cap on the opposite side of the text. On the front of the lamp there is a
                           piece of paper taped to it that reads “<placeName>LITTLE AMERICA
                              III</placeName><lb/><persName>ADM RICHARD E BYRD’S</persName><lb/>
                           <date when="1940">1940</date>-<date when="1941">41</date> EXPEDITION<lb/>
                           EMERGENCY LAMP <lb/>obt <date when="1957-03-11">3/11/57</date>” Above the
                           fuel tank there is protective <material>glass</material> around the wick,
                           this <material>glass</material> is about <dim unit="inch" quantity="4">4
                              inches</dim> tall and has crisscrossing <material>metal
                              wire</material> around it. The glass is dirty and clouded. There are
                           two tubes extending on opposite sides around the glass towards the top
                           for ventilation. There are holes around the top of the lantern for
                           ventilation and at the very top there is a loop for hanging the lantern
                           as well as a handle. </p>
                     </objectDesc>
                  </physDesc>
               </object>
               <object>
                  <objectIdentifier>
                     <country>United States of America</country>
                     <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                     <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                     <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                     <objectName>Seabees Plaque</objectName>
                  </objectIdentifier>
                  <physDesc>
                     <objectDesc>
                        <p>A large wooden <objectType>plaque</objectType> in the shape of a shield
                           with a painted circular illustration in the center.</p>
                     </objectDesc>
                     <typeDesc>
                        <p>On the inside of the circle at the very top there is the text “U.S. NAVAL
                           MOBILE CONSTRUCTION BATTALION (SPECIAL)” in large, capital sans-serif
                           block letters. The bottom of the circle has text that reads “DEEPFREEZE
                           II” with ice on top of the letters in the same typeface.</p>
                     </typeDesc>
                     <decoDesc>
                        <p>The illustration is circular with painted rope around it decorated with
                           snow and ice at the very top. In the bottom left is a gold
                              <orgName>United States</orgName> Naval Aviator Badge while to the
                           right is an illustration of a penguin. Featured in the center of the
                           illustration is a map of Antarctica with small red anchors placed where
                              <country>American</country> bases are located. Slightly obscuring this
                           map is a large illustration of the Construction Battalion logo – the
                           Seabee, a large bee with construction tools – in a winter jacket, hat and
                           earmuffs. Above the bee is the acronym “IGY” for the International
                           Geophysical Year along with the years “<date when="1957">1957</date> -
                              <date when="1958">1958</date>”.</p>
                     </decoDesc>
                  </physDesc>
               </object>
            </listObject>
         </p>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
