<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<?xml-model href="out/SectorDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Title</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Publication Information</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Information about the source</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text>
      <body>
         <listObject>
            <object>
               <objectIdentifier>
                  <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                  <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                  <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                  <objectName>Navy Icebreaker Model</objectName>
               </objectIdentifier>
               <physDesc>
                  <objectDesc>
                     <p>A detailed <objectType>model</objectType> of a wind-class ice breaker ship.
                        The hull of the ship is painted red while there is grey paint on the sides
                        above the waterline and on the roof, the deck is a light tan color and the
                        small propellers at the back of the ship are gold. The ship is labelled
                        “GB3” in four places along the waterline of the ship, two at either side of
                        the bow and two at the stern.</p>
                     <sectorDesc place="deck">Around the entire deck are small guard
                        rails.</sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="bow">At the bow there is a large, gray, armored gun that
                        sits in the center of the deck. Behind it are two smaller, black, unshielded
                        guns.</sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="sides">On the starboard and port sides there are lifeboats
                        with cranes.</sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="stern">At the stern, there is a helipad and helicopter
                        hangar with a small orange model of a Sikorsky naval helicopter. At the
                        stern railing there is a small American flag flying. </sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="center">At the center of the ship there is a large radar
                        unit, broken mast with a variety of maritime flags flying and a large
                        ventilation shaft.</sectorDesc>
                  </objectDesc>
               </physDesc>
            </object>
            <object>
               <objectIdentifier>
                  <country>United States of America</country>
                  <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                  <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                  <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                  <objectName>Armored Vehicle</objectName>
               </objectIdentifier>
               <physDesc>
                  <objectDesc>
                     <p>A small <objectType>model</objectType> of a rectangular armored vehicle with
                        treads.</p>
                     <sectorDesc place="interior">The cabin of the vehicle is shaped like a
                        rectangular prism with seven glassless, rectangular windows; two on each
                        side, one in the front and one in the back. Inside the driver’s seat there
                        is a small bar apparatus for steering, there is no seat in the passenger
                        side and instead it is blocked with a console.</sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="exterior">Within the treads there are twelve wheels on each
                        side. The driver and passenger side doors are printed with the text
                        “USN54-25026”. The front hood has a tow hook and winch, headlights and a few
                        other various mechanical apparatuses. The back trunk has a model fire axe
                        and shovel attached to it. <damage>The top of the vehicle has an antenna
                           that has been bent flat. At several of the hard corners and edges of the
                           truck, the paint has been touched up with a slightly different shade of
                           orange.</damage></sectorDesc>
                  </objectDesc>
                  <decoDesc>
                     <p>It is almost entirely painted orange except for its treads, which are black,
                        and the suspension wheels within the treads, which are green.</p>
                  </decoDesc>
               </physDesc>
            </object>
            <object>
               <objectIdentifier>
                  <institution>Florida State University</institution>
                  <repository>FSU Special Collections</repository>
                  <collection>Robert E Hancock Jr. Collection</collection>
                  <objectName>Emergency Lantern</objectName>
               </objectIdentifier>
               <physDesc>
                  <objectDesc>
                     <p>A large, <material>metal</material> emergency
                           <objectType>lantern</objectType> that is about <dim unit="feet"
                           quantity="1">1 foot</dim> tall. It is silver colored metal with a
                        tarnished, dirty exterior. </p>
                     <sectorDesc place="base">The lantern has a circular fuel tank base that is
                        about <dim unit="inch" quantity="2">2 inches</dim> tall with HERCULES
                        printed in large letters on the front of it. There is also a small fuel cap
                        on the opposite side of the text. On the front of the lamp there is a piece
                        of paper taped to it that reads “<placeName>LITTLE AMERICA
                           III</placeName><lb/><persName>ADM RICHARD E BYRD’S</persName><lb/>
                        <date when="1940">1940</date>-<date when="1941">41</date> EXPEDITION<lb/>
                        EMERGENCY LAMP <lb/>obt <date when="1957-03-11">3/11/57</date>”</sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="lamp">Above the fuel tank there is protective
                           <material>glass</material> around the wick, this
                           <material>glass</material> is about <dim unit="inch" quantity="4">4
                           inches</dim> tall and has crisscrossing <material>metal wire</material>
                        around it. The glass is dirty and clouded. There are two tubes extending on
                        opposite sides around the glass towards the top for
                        ventilation.</sectorDesc>
                     <sectorDesc place="lid">There are holes around the top of the lantern for
                        ventilation and at the very top there is a loop for hanging the lantern as
                        well as a handle. </sectorDesc>
                  </objectDesc>
               </physDesc>
            </object>
         </listObject>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
